A Guide to the Additional Papers of Harry F. Byrd, Jr., ca. 1924-2003
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series V: Plaques Awarded to Harry F. Byrd and Byrd Miscellany
  - Virginia Military Institute for Distinguished Service 1975 (Oversize Box S-78)
  - The American Legion Special Commendation for Byrd's opposition to the surrender of the Panama Canal 1978 (Oversize Box S-78)
  - Build America Better Award 1982 (Oversize Box S-78)
  - Douglas MacArthur Chapter Association of the United States Army Meritorious Service Award 1978 Feb 28 (Oversize Box S-79)
  - To Harry F. Byrd, Jr. for his Tireless Dedication to the Cause of a Free Cuba 1982 Dec (Oversize Box S-79)
  - Certificate of Appreciation from Winchester, Frederick and Clarke Counties for Outstanding and Dedicated Service 1983 (Oversize Box S-79)
  - City of Hampton July 9, 1610 Plate n.d. (Oversize Box S-79)
  - God and Country Campaign Southwest Baptist Church 1974 Nov 17 (Oversize Box S-80)
  - Chabad Lubavitch of Virginia on occasion of 75th Birthday of Rabbi Menachem M. Schneerson 1977 Mar 30 (Oversize Box S-80)
  - In Appreciation for years of unlimited service rendered to the Disabled American Veterans 1979 (Oversize Box S-80)
  - In Appreciation of Faithful Service to Our Community Shenandoah Valley Baptist Church 1982 (Oversize Box S-80)
  - Liberty Bell Award Law Day USA 3-May-82 (Oversize Box S-80)
  - Tax Executives Institute, Inc. Certificate of Appreciation 1982 Mar 24 (Oversize Box S-81)
  - The VMI Corporate Affiliate Program recognizes Winchester Evening Star as a Member 1982-1983 (Oversize Box S-81)
  - The American Farm Bureau Federation Award for Distinguished and Meritorious Service 1983 Jan 11 (Oversize Box S-81)
  - Virginia Nursing Home Association Public Service Award 1974 (Oversize Box S-82)
  - Shenandoah Valley National Bank to Byrd Family of Virginia for 50 Years of Service 1980 (Oversize Box S-82)
  - Americans for Constitutional Action Distinguished Service Award 1980 Jun 17 (Oversize Box S-82)
  - Key to City of Alexandria n.d. (Oversize Box S-82)
  - Jefferson's Poplar Forest Restoration Poster 1984-1986 (Oversize folder 1 (OS Tray 251):)
  - Shenandoah National Park Fiftieth Anniversary Print signed by Lawrence Ormsby of "Virginia White-tailed Deer" 1986 (Oversize folder 1 (OS Tray 251):)
  - United States Seal n.d. (Oversize folder 1 (OS Tray 251):)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce Distinguished Service Award 1976 (Oversize folder 1 (OS Tray 251):)
  - Blueprint of the Press Room at the The News-Record, Harrisonburg, Virginia by the American Type Founders Engineering Department (oversize) 1940 Sep 28 (Oversize folder 2 (OS Box T-31):)
  - Campaign Poster (oversize) n.d. (Oversize folder 2 (OS Box T-31):)
  - Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. in a Senate meeting and Harry F. Byrd, Sr. with Conrad Wirth, Director of the National Park Service (oversize) 1965, 1982 (Oversize folder 2 (OS Box T-31):)
  - Print of the Executive Mansion by Vernon P. Johnson (No. 66 of 950) - oversize 1987 (Oversize folder 2 (OS Box T-31):)
  - Seibel Cartoon "Byrd Watchers" (2 copies) 1960 Aug 23, 1965 (Oversize folder 2 (OS Box T-31):)
    Nashville Banner "A Place in the Gallery of the Great" cartoon, and Senate Memorial for Harry F. Byrd, Sr.: oversize
  - West Richmond Businessmen's Association Resolutions (oversize) 1983, 1988 (Oversize folder 2 (OS Box T-31):)
  - Woodrow Wilson Birthplace Foundation honorary membership (oversize) n.d. (Oversize folder 2 (OS Box T-31):)
  - Small U.S. flags, 1979 (Oversize Box (T-31))
    small and large Virginia flags, and one small Winchester, Virginia flag, taken to the South Pole by Senator Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (oversize)
  - American Flag - "This flag was flown over the Capitol and Drapped the Casket of Senator Harry F. Byrd, Sr." (oversize) 1966 (Oversize Box (T-31))
  - 2 American Flags (oversize) n.d. (Oversize Box (T-31))
  - Virginia Association of Broadcasters "Distinguished Virginian" award 1984 (Oversize Box (T-31))
    consisting of commemorative metal plates featuring four famous Virginia buildings, Monticello, the Capitol Building in Williamsburg, St. Johns Church, Richmond, and Mt. Vernon, mounted on a blue background (OS box H-14)
  - "Fall Guy" portrait of Senator Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1981 Sep 25 (Oversize Box (T-31))
    Virginia Saints & Sinners, Richmond, Virginia, charcoal and pencil drawing of Byrd covered with autographs (1M carrel H)
  - U.S. Bicentennial Print of a painting "Prayer at Valley Forge" by Arnold Friberg, presented to Byrd by the Paul Carrington Chapter, S.A.R. (1M carrel H) 1982 Feb 17 (Oversize Box (T-31))